<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Indigenous Physicians Association of Canada]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Indigenous Physicians Association of Canada]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 19:54:35 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Our Beliefs & Values]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Our Beliefs & Values</h1><p>IPAC’s beliefs and values originate from communities, our ancestors and the teachings found within our cultures. We believe that Indigenous People deserve the best health possible. We honour the wholistic view of health (body, mind, spirit and heart) including traditional knowledge and practices. We believe that Indigenous physicians are honoured with positions of trust in the communities and commitment to our responsibilities are reflected in our work.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/our-beliefs-and-values/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3cc7f3f7-e883-4ff4-b78d-567a166809c3</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 19:54:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>As Indigenous physicians and students, diversely rooted in our traditional teachings and our respective communities, IPAC embraces and commits to the responsibility to work together to use our skills, abilities and experiences to advance the health of our nations, communities, families and individuals.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/36a6d8a5-2eb0-4abd-bc7f-9f32c3b210ce/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">36a6d8a5-2eb0-4abd-bc7f-9f32c3b210ce</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 19:54:07 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>IPAC holds a vision of healthy and vibrant Indigenous nations, communities, families and individuals, who are supported by an abundance of well-educated, well-supported Indigenous physicians working with those who contribute to the physical, mental, emotional and spiritual well-being of our peoples and communities which has a positive impact on the social determinants of health.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/cf64f433-65f0-4674-b5d1-d1c106adfdcc/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">cf64f433-65f0-4674-b5d1-d1c106adfdcc</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 19:53:48 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>Greetings from Indigenous Physicians, MDs from across Canada who share a common mission to improve the health of Indigenous Peoples and enhance the role of Indigenous Physicians in health provision, design and setting priorities.  We collaborate with physicians in training and practice, other health professionals, communities, agencies, and governments to ultimately improve Indigenous health.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/indigenous-physicians-association-of-canada/greetings-from-indigenous-physicians-mds-from-across-canada/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3fc277fb-1bb5-40e9-99ba-4393af648d9c</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2016 19:47:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>